

NATALIE SOBERANO

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

416-817-7729

NatalieSoberano@yahoo.ca

458 Melrose Avenue | Toronto, ON | M5M 1Z9

Matalie Soberano

EDUCATION

Western University/ Fanshawe College

[2016 - 2020] Bachelor of Arts in Media, Information & Technoculture

Diploma in Interactive Media Design

Dean's Honour List 80% Average [2017 - 2019]

Tanenbaum CHAT
High School
[2012 - 2016]

COMMUNITY SERVICE

OHM Charity Fashion

Show

[2019 - Present] Senior graphic designer in creating all visual branding.

Chabad Western

[2018 - Present] Graphic designer for all promotional content.

Swim Ability London

[2016 - 2017]
Part-time swim instructor to children with disabilities.

Crafting For A CureWestern

[2017 - 2018] Brining arts & crafts activities to kids in hospitals as a way to brighten their day.

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a university student at Western University and Fanshawe College in London, Ontario. I am in a dual program between both schools currently studying media, theory and production. I have previously worked as a graphic designer/intern for Ink Entertainment and LUG Hockey. This taught me workplace values such as self-confidence, orginization, creativity, leadership and emotional intelligence - ability to read peoples' nonverbal cues and the ability to manage oneself within a team. Moreover, I am extremely hardworking and I am passionate about all things I participate in.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Graphic Design Intern: Ink Entertainment [May - June 2017 & July 2019 - Present]

144 Bloor St W, 7th Floor, Toronto, ON M5S 1M4

Worked and created a variety of different design projects, weekly newsletters, blog posts and various promotional content.

Skills Developed: This internship taught me the skills required to working in the environment of a graphic designer such as collaboration and creative thinking. It allowed me to take a creative vision and design a professional peice.

Graphic Designer: LUG Hocky [June 2018 - Present]

Worked on a variety of different design projects, promotional content and merchandise.

Skills Developed: This position has taught me how to take the vision of a client and create a usable product. It has furthered my skills in design and has taught me to be vigilant with deadlines.

Graphic Designer: The Paper Pantry [September 2019 - Present]

Created card and invitation designs on a freelance basis.

Skills Developed: This position has allowed me to be creative and bring a vision to life in a timely fashion.

Camp Councillor: Camp Shalom [July - August 2016 & 2017]

Worked as a camp councillor for twelve - thirteen year olds and as a swim instructor and lifegaurd for children six - thirteen

SKILLS

- PhotoshopIllustratorInDesignTypography
- PackagingAfter EffectsCinema 4DHTML & CSS (Front End Coding)